<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Troika 2014</string>
    <string name="title_events">Events</string>
    <string name="title_register">Register</string>
    <string name="title_contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_about">About</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="contact_fragment_placeholder">Contact Fragment</string>
    <string name="event_fragment_placeholder">Events Fragment</string>
    <string name="register_fragment_placeholder">Register Fragment</string>

    <string-array name="event_titles">
        <item>bits</item>
        <item>bots</item>
        <item>brainwave</item>
        <item>bytes</item>
        <item>design_pro</item>
        <item>electrocution</item>
        <item>envision</item>
        <item>ether_avatar</item>
        <item>inspironnature</item>
        <item>junkyard</item>
        <item>mist</item>
        <item>radix</item>
        <item>spac</item>
        <item>technovision</item>
        <item>todo_en_uno</item>
        <item>vihaan</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="event_names">
        <item>Bits</item>
        <item>Bots</item>
        <item>Brainwave</item>
        <item>Bytes</item>
        <item>"Design Pro"</item>
        <item>Electrocution</item>
        <item>Envision</item>
        <item>"Ether Avatar"</item>
        <item>Inspironature</item>
        <item>Junkyard</item>
        <item>Mist</item>
        <item>Radix</item>
        <item>SPAC</item>
        <item>Technovision</item>
        <item>"Todo En Uno"</item>
        <item>Vihaan</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="event_descriptions">
        <!--bits-->
        <item>"Most good programmers do programming not because they expect to get paid or get
            adulation by the public, but because it is fun to program.
            -Linus Torvalds

            So put yourself in front of your prized laptops and desktops, revise your programming
            skills and let in a breath of fresh air as TROIKA 2014 brings to you BITS- The on the
            spot programming competition.

            To keep alive the avid programmer inside you, this contest is back and will prove to
            satisfy your programming cravings and examine your knowledge of programming languages
            like C, C++ and JAVA in a specified limited time frame as well.

            Your capability and creativity will be rigorously tested not only on a single level but
            on a multitude of levels. This contest will involve a combination of various rounds
            which will include different problem statements. BITS is a golden opportunity for the
            geek inside you to create, innovate and produce avant-garde programs.

            Ready? On your marks, get, set.. GO!"
        </item>
        <!--bots-->
        <item>"While ( ! ( succeed=try () ) ) ;

            Do you consider yourself as having the capability to design a programme that will defend
            you from the blows and punches of the opponent's programme efficaciously and fight back
            at the same time with that same programme at your rescue?

            If your answer is a yes, then prepare yourselves for the ultimate programming
            extravaganza as TROIKA 2014 presents to you BOTS- the AI gaming challenge. This
            competition utilizes your ability to formulate your gaming strategy not once but again
            and again, consider the pros and cons that are involved with each decisive move of yours
            and devise a calculative plan that will become game changing not only for you but your
            opponent as well.

            Apply your coding wit and grit to develop a program that not only runs with perfection
            but rather runs over the program of your adversary and hence, defeats it to emerge
            victorious in the end. Effective scheming and planning along with error free and
            effective programming is all that's required.

            So are you prepped up for some action?"
        </item>
        <!--brainwave-->
        <item>"Are you enthralled by the fact that how a single click of yours opens up a kinky
            &amp; glittery world of gadgetry, that you love to dwell in for hours???

            If hitherto your head nods in a yes, then with certainty I say WAVES of catechism
            pertaining to the world of embedded systems would barrage your BRAIN.

            BRAINWAVE is the destination you must set for yourself. BRAINWAVE is the ultimate
            hardware design challenge with a special focus on the implementation and augmentation
            gratifying your Electronics appetite to a level of surfeit. The moment has dawned upon
            once gain...and its time you showcase your brain and win waves of accolades by playing
            with that small gizmo that you have, the MICROCONTROLLER! "
        </item>
        <!--bytes-->
        <item>"Crack your knuckles and get yourselves geared up for BYTES- The online coding contest
            brought to you by TROIKA 2014. If you are easily enticed by challenging programmes,
            tempted to crack difficult algorithms and consider programming as easy as your mother
            tongue, then your wait is almost over now as this is THE event for the avid programmer
            in you.

            BYTES is an ultimate platform to code which gives you an opportunity to apply your
            expertise in programming and henceforth lets you to devise astute algorithms and create
            ingenious programmes. With the swift and decisive tap of your fingertips, fabricate
            exquisite codes while blending enormous amounts of creativity in it and pour knowledge
            into this mixing pot of BYTES to concoct arete programs that work with absolute
            perfection, impeccable precision and have the capability to amaze!

            Go on and participate to give yourself a programming treat!"
        </item>
        <!--design-pro-->
        <!--electrocution-->
        <!--envision-->
        <!--ether-avatar-->
        <!--inspironnature-->
        <!--junkyard-->
        <!--mist-->
        <!--radix-->
        <!--spac-->
        <!--technovision-->
        <!--todoenuno-->
        <!--vihaan-->


    </string-array>


</resources>
