<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Troika 2014</string>
    <string name="title_events">Events</string>
    <string name="title_register">Register</string>
    <string name="title_contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_about">About</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="contact_fragment_placeholder">Contact Fragment</string>
    <string name="event_fragment_placeholder">Events Fragment</string>
    <string name="register_fragment_placeholder">Register Fragment</string>

    <string-array name="event_titles">
        <item>bits</item>
        <item>bots</item>
        <item>brainwave</item>
        <item>bytes</item>
        <item>design_pro</item>
        <item>electrocution</item>
        <item>envision</item>
        <item>ether_avatar</item>
        <item>inspironnature</item>
        <item>junkyard</item>
        <item>mist</item>
        <item>radix</item>
        <item>spac</item>
        <item>technovision</item>
        <item>todo_en_uno</item>
        <item>vihaan</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="event_names">
        <item>Bits</item>
        <item>Bots</item>
        <item>Brainwave</item>
        <item>Bytes</item>
        <item>"Design Pro"</item>
        <item>Electrocution</item>
        <item>Envision</item>
        <item>"Ether Avatar"</item>
        <item>Inspironature</item>
        <item>Junkyard</item>
        <item>Mist</item>
        <item>Radix</item>
        <item>SPAC</item>
        <item>Technovision</item>
        <item>"Todo En Uno"</item>
        <item>Vihaan</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="event_descriptions">
        <!--bits-->
        <item>"Most good programmers do programming not because they expect to get paid or get
            adulation by the public, but because it is fun to program.
            -Linus Torvalds

            So put yourself in front of your prized laptops and desktops, revise your programming
            skills and let in a breath of fresh air as TROIKA 2014 brings to you BITS- The on the
            spot programming competition.

            To keep alive the avid programmer inside you, this contest is back and will prove to
            satisfy your programming cravings and examine your knowledge of programming languages
            like C, C++ and JAVA in a specified limited time frame as well.

            Your capability and creativity will be rigorously tested not only on a single level but
            on a multitude of levels. This contest will involve a combination of various rounds
            which will include different problem statements. BITS is a golden opportunity for the
            geek inside you to create, innovate and produce avant-garde programs.

            Ready? On your marks, get, set.. GO!"
        </item>
        <!--bots-->
        <item>"While ( ! ( succeed=try () ) ) ;

            Do you consider yourself as having the capability to design a programme that will defend
            you from the blows and punches of the opponent's programme efficaciously and fight back
            at the same time with that same programme at your rescue?

            If your answer is a yes, then prepare yourselves for the ultimate programming
            extravaganza as TROIKA 2014 presents to you BOTS- the AI gaming challenge. This
            competition utilizes your ability to formulate your gaming strategy not once but again
            and again, consider the pros and cons that are involved with each decisive move of yours
            and devise a calculative plan that will become game changing not only for you but your
            opponent as well.

            Apply your coding wit and grit to develop a program that not only runs with perfection
            but rather runs over the program of your adversary and hence, defeats it to emerge
            victorious in the end. Effective scheming and planning along with error free and
            effective programming is all that's required.

            So are you prepped up for some action?"
        </item>
        <!--brainwave-->
        <item>"Are you enthralled by the fact that how a single click of yours opens up a kinky
            &amp; glittery world of gadgetry, that you love to dwell in for hours???

            If hitherto your head nods in a yes, then with certainty I say WAVES of catechism
            pertaining to the world of embedded systems would barrage your BRAIN.

            BRAINWAVE is the destination you must set for yourself. BRAINWAVE is the ultimate
            hardware design challenge with a special focus on the implementation and augmentation
            gratifying your Electronics appetite to a level of surfeit. The moment has dawned upon
            once gain...and its time you showcase your brain and win waves of accolades by playing
            with that small gizmo that you have, the MICROCONTROLLER! "
        </item>
        <!--bytes-->
        <item>"Crack your knuckles and get yourselves geared up for BYTES- The online coding contest
            brought to you by TROIKA 2014. If you are easily enticed by challenging programmes,
            tempted to crack difficult algorithms and consider programming as easy as your mother
            tongue, then your wait is almost over now as this is THE event for the avid programmer
            in you.

            BYTES is an ultimate platform to code which gives you an opportunity to apply your
            expertise in programming and henceforth lets you to devise astute algorithms and create
            ingenious programmes. With the swift and decisive tap of your fingertips, fabricate
            exquisite codes while blending enormous amounts of creativity in it and pour knowledge
            into this mixing pot of BYTES to concoct arete programs that work with absolute
            perfection, impeccable precision and have the capability to amaze!

            Go on and participate to give yourself a programming treat!"
        </item>
        <!--design-pro-->
        <item>"Creativity is more than just being different. Anybody can plan weird; that's easy.
            What’s hard is to be as simple as Bach. Making the simple, awesomely simple, that's
            creativity
            - Charles Mingus

            Design Pro is an innovative event that challenges the creative bug in you. To master
            this event, you need to be a proficient image designer, web developer or animator, any
            one of them. The event is sub-divided into three categories:

            Animax: The ultimate Animation Challenge
            CreatX: The graphic designing contest.
            Webimax: On the spot web development competition.

            Everything we see on the web, be it a sterling website, an awe-inspiring animation or
            the attention grabbing posters and banners, all are a result of background work of few
            visionary creative geniuses who are able to couple their technical brilliance with
            creative propensity and deliver visually striking products, which can gather the
            necessary audience.

            Design pro is the perfect place for creative geniuses who can design the most wondrous
            website that leaves people awestruck or a prodigious animation that will cause even the
            makers of 'Shrek' and 'Up' to envy you and those of 'Life of Pi' to rethink.

            Let your imagination come to the fore, dig up your creative resources to find the right
            mix of creative supplements to showcase your ingenious skills and style."
        </item>
        <!--electrocution-->
        <item>"Ever dreamt of being bombarded by a stream of resistors, diodes, capacitors and
            inductors? If yes then its time you take your revenge, enslave them and play with them!

            TROIKA 14 presents to you the event ELECTROCUTION which will scrutinize the Ohm, Farad
            and Henry within you and will hallmark you as the wizard of circuits, if you emerge as
            the winner. Practical knowledge sandwiched by what you learned within the walls of the
            classroom is what you require to attain the ultimate glory.

            So let the frenzy, furor and fuss of the circuits run through your blood and prepare
            yourself not to get ELECTROCUTED!"
        </item>
        <!--envision-->
        <item>"It's OK to figure out murder mysteries, but you shouldn't need to figure out code.
            You should be able to read it
            - Steve McConnell

            Software development is the versatile equivalent of poetry and prose to engineers. A
            flair for coding, even if a budding one, should be pursued through various
            opportunities. Such an opportunity comes along your way in the form of Envision, a
            software conceptualizing event in TROIKA 2014.

            Envision is a virtual playground, where survival of the deftest prevails. The event
            consists of two categories -

            1. Ingenuity (open coding)
            2. Dexterity (predefined coding)

            These two categories will ensure that the coder isn't left devoid of any finesse that
            he/she has. There is always a need of software innovation in this dynamic technocracy.
            Team TROIKA will guarantee that the people tend to this need and nurture them into the
            adept engineers that they will be."
        </item>
        <!--ether-avatar-->
        <item>"
            Ignorance is the curse of God;
            Knowledge is the wing wherewith we fly to heaven.
            -William Shakespeare

            Knowledge is a word which you can define in as many ways as you want to. But for us at
            IEEE-DTU, knowledge is what helps you master Ether Avatar.

            Ether Avatar is a LAN quizzing event wherein everyone will be simultaneously attempting
            the quiz by typing in their answers on the computers that we provide at the venue. Ether
            will test your knowledge based on anything and everything under the sun. You can be
            asked questions from Science, Technology, Business, Mythology, Entertainment,
            Literature, Sports, Geography, Heritage, Politics and what not. But it’s not just
            knowledge that you will require. Climbing the Ether ladder requires a combination of
            impeccable presence of mind, quick thinking and perfect ability to connect the dots in
            addition to comprehensive knowledge.

            The bug of curiosity you have been sheltering since time immemorial will be put to test
            when the best of the best quizzers, knowledge enthusiasts and geeks of Delhi and around
            will be pitted against each other in an ever so thrilling encounter.

            So if you think you know A LOT of things about A LOT of things, if you think you can
            crack anything and everything put forward to you from the vast never ending world of
            general knowledge, if you think you have the true quizzing spirit in you, Ether is the
            event for you to participate."
        </item>
        <!--inspironnature-->
        <item>"
            I learnt from the sun
            That light has to be spread,
            The breeze taught me
            How to be cool all the time
            The trees inspired me to be colossal in giving
            As I discovered serenity from water
            And the vacuum made me understand
            How to live with nothing around
            For nature had all virtues a man needs to learn
            In all its elements

            Inspironature, an event to mimic nature's phenomenon provides you with an opportunity to
            ideate and innovate to design instrument for the benefit of mankind. Its working or
            principle should be based on the natural processes or the natural scheme of events that
            you see around in your environment. So use all your grey matter and be vigilant about
            the vibrant nature and its phenomenon and principles. Mimic nature's principles and
            mould them into an idea of your own instrument.

            So use all your grey matter and be vigilant about the vibrant nature and its phenomenon
            and principles. Mimic nature's principles and mould them into an idea of your own
            instrument. "
        </item>
        <!--junkyard-->
        <item>"Creativity is not the finding of a thing, but the making something out of it after it
            is found.

            Man has designed innumerable ingenious mechanisms to simplify his day to day life. So,
            what about making tools out of waste? Can scrap be used to make useful machinery?

            Junkyard aims to answer such questions and that too in a fun way. Junkyard provides a
            platform for those creative genii in you, who like to think out of the box. To excel in
            this competition you just need to have loads of enthusiasm, tons of perseverance,
            tolerance to a high magnitude of dirt &amp; grease and zeal of innovation.

            In this event, you will be provided with problem statements and the junk. All you have
            to do is use your technical knowhow coupled with your "Jugaad" skills to find just the
            right tools and scrap, enabling you to provide solutions to solve the problem
            statements.

            There is just one GOLDEN RULE that there is no GOLDEN RULE.

            For all those who consider themselves mechanical geniuses or creative maniacs, it's time
            to break free! Enter the battlefield of trash and put your innovative skills to work!

            Use your imagination and bring to life your brainchild for everyone to see"
        </item>
        <!--mist-->
        <item>"
            Do you think you have what it takes to solve mysteries? Do you sometimes feel that you
            would have been better suited in the shoes of detective?z

            As Troika is eagerly awaited, we foray into yet another, highly anticipated edition of
            MIST, the online treasure hunt guaranteed to force your brain into overdrive. Challenge
            your mental faculties, as your lateral thinking skills are pushed to the utmost limit.
            Attack levels with the ferocity of a tiger, while dodging traps with the dexterity of a
            snake. Battle it out with participants all around the globe, with the added satisfaction
            of gaining bragging rights.

            MIST is bigger, better and far more challenging than it has ever been. No mere mortal
            will survive this quest. Establish yourself as the last-man standing, one who has passed
            all tests of endurance, and reach out for the coveted pinnacle of the leaderboard, while
            fending off dangers from your rivals.

            Welcome aboard. Great treasures await you."
        </item>
        <!--radix-->
        <item>"

            Tighten the screws and oil your brain
            For those who stand strong, no effort goes in vain.

            Do you nurture an inherent desire within the deep strata of your heart to control the
            world? If yes, then the time has come when you can shine as the master of if not people
            around you but certainly the ROBOTS created by YOU!

            TROIKA '14 presents RADIX, the Robotics carnival which will provide you the steps to
            attain the zenith of Robotics and emerge as the master. You will be obliged to bisect
            your focus equally between mechanical and autonomous events, with fighting, outracing
            and manipulating others bots to emerge as the ultimate winner.

            So create a slave of your own and use it to be the master of all!!"
        </item>
        <!--spac-->
        <item>"The true sense of intelligence is not knowledge but inspiration.
            -Albert Einstein

            Upon graduating, Should I join a company or should I go for research? Should I pursue
            higher studies or should I try to open a start-up?

            Career-oriented questions like these bother us all the time. Here is an opportunity for
            you to get answers to all such queries at SPAC 2014.

            SPAC, Student Professional Awareness Conference, aims to bridge the gap between the
            professional needs of technologists-in-training and wisdom of technology leaders from
            different fields. It provides the perfect platform to not only increase professional
            awareness among engineering students but also helps them widen their view on the real
            world.

            So, spark your career by being a part of this conference that congregates the knowledge
            and expertise of esteemed and successful engineers and industrialists!"
        </item>
        <!--technovision-->
        <item>"Hold your breaths my dear technical researchers; we bring to you Technovision, the
            technical research paper presentation competition to be held during Troika '14- the
            annual tech-fest of IEEE-DTU Chapter.

            If you aim to become a real life Sheldon Cooper and your place of worship is the lab of
            your college, then Technovision is the event for you.

            Through Technovision, we aim to bring out the impeccable observational skills of people
            with scientifically oriented minds, in their fields of interest ranging from
            Electronics, Electricals and Computers to Bio-Technology and Chemistry. The thorough
            study and comprehensive research done by the budding young minds of our country can be
            showcased through their research papers, also testing their sharp presentation skills at
            the same time.

            So for all the budding research scholars and prospective Nobel Laureates, Technovision
            is THE event for you. Show off your research, receive accolades and the chance to get
            your paper published in a recognized journal."
        </item>
        <!--todoenuno-->
        <item>"

            How long did it take you to solve the level-3 Sudoku?
            Hey, what would be the trick solving this puzzle?

            If these questions comprise your candid conversations, then look no further. Troika 2014
            is pleased to announce the IQ- quizzing competition, Todo-en-Uno, as part of its roster
            of various events.

            As the name translates into Spanish as 'All in one', the competition will ensure the
            meaning of the name. The quizzing event will cover the entire spectrum of knowledge
            including logic, puzzles, code breaking, encryption, mathematics, anagrams, matrix and
            pictoral conundrums, and audiovisual rounds.

            So put your thinking caps on and tackle the trivia maze.

            Get connected to our Facebook page for more updates."
        </item>
        <!--vihaan-->
        <item>"While her friends played with Barbie dolls, she was busy playing with technology, and
            creating the future. Such is a story of a woman in engineering

            IEEE Women in Engineering (WIE) is the largest international professional organization
            dedicated to promoting women engineers and scientists and inspiring girls around the
            world to follow their academic interests to a career in engineering.

            With this thought we present to you VIHAAN, the event organized by WIE IEEE that aims to
            create a new beginning for women in engineering by providing them a unique opportunity
            to participate in a girls' only coding competition that aims to test your intelligence
            and grasping power. Be a part of the event and share our vision of a vibrant community
            of women and men collectively using their diverse talents to innovate for the benefit of
            humanity."
        </item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="contact_title">
        <item>"President"</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="contact_name">
        <item>"Rishi Pandey</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="contact_phone">
        <item>"999999999"</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="contact_email">
        <item>"somebody@something.com"</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
